A Guide to the Maps and flat files FA465
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Pocantico Hills, 6
  - 7 architectural blueprints: "Swimming Pool for JDR, Jr. at Pocantico Hills, NY." (architect Duncan Candler), 1937 September; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 7) (Drawer B 15, Folder 1)
    PH-76B, 78A, 78
  - Map of Lands to be Conveyed by John D. Rockefeller, Jr. to Tarrytown., 1945 January 22; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 15, Folder 2)
    PH-97
  - Map of Four Parcels of Property Belonging to John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Situated in Mt. Pleasant., 1943 November 23; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 15, Folder 2)
    PH-96
  - Topographical Map of Buttermilk Hill, Pocantico Hills, NY, 1943 March; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 15, Folder 2)
    PH-93 #2
  - "The Topographic Maps of the United States." Color map and article on Buttermilk Hill., 1902; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 15, Folder 2)
    PH-93
  - Photocopy showing blowup of Buttermilk Hill from color map listed above. Amended to showing distance to Chappaqua Hill from Buttermilk Hill., MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 15, Folder 2)
  - Map of Lands to be Acquired for the Saw Mill River Parkway, 1941 June 18; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 15, Folder 3)
  - Map of Lands to be Acquired for the Saw Mill River Parkway., 1932 April 6; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 15, Folder 3)
    PH-83A
  - Map of Lands to be Acquired for the Saw Mill River Parkway., 1941 December 10; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 15, Folder 3)
  - [Portion of]Section Map # 5, Earl B. Lovell survey, amended: 1933 March 30; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 15, Folder 3)
    PH-82
    Map covers the area between Bedford Road, Weber Ave, Cottage Street, and Amos Street in Sleepy Hollow.
  - "Sanitary Sewerage System of Pocantico Hills, NY." (Walter Kidde Constructors Inc.), 1931 December; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 15, Folder 3)
    PH-80
  - Map Showing exchange of property between John D. Rockefeller Jr. and estate of Antonio Manna., 1940 May 25; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 15, Folder 3)
    PH-81
  - "Topographic Survey prepared for David M. Milton esquire at Pocantico Hills, NY." (Walter Kidde Constructors Inc.), 1939 May 22; MAP (Quantity 1). Oversized. (Drawer B 15, Folder 3)
    PH-790
  - "Survey of Property prepared for John D. Rockefeller Jr." Survey of Mrs. Milton's property. (Walter Kidde Constructors Inc.), 1939 July 25; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1). Oversized. (Drawer B 15, Folder 3)
    PH-79B
  - Topographical survey map of property to be deeded to Mrs. Milton, 1937 October; MAP (Quantity 1). Oversized. (Drawer B 15, Folder 3)
    PH-79A
  - Map showing property to be deeded to Mrs. Milton. Prepared for John D. Rockefeller Jr. (Walter Kidde Constructors Inc.), 1938 November 21; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 15, Folder 3)
    Map # 79 Copy 1.
  - Proposed exchange of land with Mr.Stillman from Mr. Miller, 1940 October; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 15, Folder 4)
    PH 84
  - "Map of Property to be Exchanged between JDR Jr., and Estate of Antonio Manna" (Walter Kidde Constructors Inc.), 1940 May 25; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 15, Folder 4)
    ph 85
  - Record showing burial sites in green crayon: JDR Jr., burial plot and general planting plan, 1940 April 24; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 15, Folder 4)
    ph 87
  - 2 copies: "Survey of Property prepared for JDR Jr." (Walter Kidde Constructors Inc.), 1941 August 21; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 2) (Drawer B 15, Folder 4)
    ph 89
  - photocopy of "Survey of Property prepared for Rockwood Hall Inc. in the town of Mount Pleasant NY" (Ward Carpenter & Co.), 1928 January 24; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 10, Folder 2)
    PH 73
    note on back says "1928. Copy of survey map Rockwood Hall property"
  - photocopy of "Map of Parcels belonging to... John D. Rockefeller and James A. Stillman" (Ward Carpenter & Co.), 1911 January; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 10, Folder 2)
    PH 70
    note on back says "Copy 2-Stillman property - re exchange proposed"
  - blueprint of "Survey of Property prepared for JDR JR situated in the town of Mt. Pleasant" (Walter Kidde Constructors), 1940 June 24; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 10, Folder 2)
    PH 69
    notes on back read "June 1940-Survey of property deeded to Mr. Rockefeller 3rd "The Ruins"; "Survey by A.B. Miller 6/24/40", "The Ruins tract Pocantico Hills, NY"
  - "Elevations for "Houses #9 and 48 in Pocantico Village NY for JDR Jr. Esq" (Grosvenor Atterbury), 1930 October 28; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 10) (Drawer B 10, Folder 2)
    PH 72, 72B
    notes on reverse read "Atterbury plans for houses 48 and 9"; "ISSUED 10/30/30"
  - elevations for "House #10 in Pocantico Village NY for JDR JR, Esq" (Grosvenor Atterbury), 1930 October 28; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 4) (Drawer B 10, Folder 2)
    P.H. 72C
  - elevations for "Houses #10 and 46 in Pocantico Village NY for JDR JR Esq" (Grosvenor Atterbury), 1930 October 28; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 2) (Drawer B 10, Folder 2)
  - plot plan and details from "Houses 8-9-47-48-10-46 for JDR JR" at Pocantico Hills NY (Grosvenor Atterbury), 1930 October 21, October 28; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 2) (Drawer B 10, Folder 2)
    one is marked P.H. 72D
  - "Map of lands to be acquired for the Saw Mill River Parkway" (Westchester County Park Commission), 1930 February 6; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 10, Folder 2)
    PH 62
    note on reverse "2/18/30 Saw Mill river parkway - re exchange with NY Central RR. From Mr. Downer. Corr in 169 N51" other handwritten notes
  - Goldstone adn Hinz Architects maps of Pocantico Hills properties, 1978-1979; 20 color photocopies with index. (Drawer D 13, Folder 4)
    Planned division of Pocantico Hills estate.
  - Chas. H. Sells maps of Pocantico Hills estate, 1970; amended 1978-1979; MAP (Quantity 5) (Drawer D 13, Folder 4)
  - Hudson valley. 1 marked with historic/commercial/tourism sources. (no source), undated; Maps (Quantity 2) (Drawer E 8, Folder 1)
  - Saw Mill River/Ardsley Flood Protection Project (NYS Dept. of Environmental Conservation), 1989 November 1; Map (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 8, Folder 1)
  - 3 sets of packet "Topographical survey of Pocantico Hills Estate" with an extra sheet of accompanying map (Chas H. Sells, Inc.), 1961 June 28; MAP (Quantity 9) (Drawer E 9, Folder 1)
  - "Topographic Maps of property, Town of Mt. Pleasant", Pocantico Hills, NY marked "P.H. Contours" (Chas H. Sells/ Sasaki Associates, Inc. (Massachusetts)), 1974 November; MAP (Quantity 4) (Drawer E 9, Folder 1)
  - booklet of topographic surveys of Pocantico Hills Estate, Westchester County, NY (Earl B. Lovell; Chas H. Sells; Lockwood, Kessler & Bartlett Inc), 1961 June 28; MAP (Quantity 9) (Drawer E 10, Folder 2)
  - series of 5 marker drawings on vellum, 1980 October 10; MAP (Quantity 5) (Drawer E 10, Folder 2)
  - map of Putnam County NY w/ highlighted areas "Garrison Golf Club", "Permanent Open Space", "Institutional Open Space", MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 10, Folder 2)
  - map of Putnam County NY "Preliminary Town of Philipstown" in 3 pieces, taped together., 1963 April 29; 1964 September 17; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 10, Folder 2)
  - topographical survey of "Pocantico Hills Housing Development Areas" with colored areas (Sasaki Associates, Inc. (Massachusetts)), 1980 October 10; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 10, Folder 2)
  - topographical survey of "Pocantico Hills Housing Development Areas" with labeling and colored details, 1930 August 13; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 10, Folder 2)
  - set of "Townscape Studies" A, B, C & existing with colored pencil shading (Sasaki Associates, Inc. (Massachusetts)), 1980 October 6; MAP (Quantity 4) (Drawer E 10, Folder 2)
  - "Pocantico Hills Housing Development Areas A, C, E, H, I-Site Utlilities" topographical survey with coloring (Sasaki Associates, Inc. (Massachusetts)), 1980 October 10; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 10, Folder 2)
  - Tarrytown Heights, Pocantico Hills and Tower Hill Stations for sale by Wilson H. Blackwell and Company, 1890s; 2 Sheets Map is split between two sheets, formerly taped together through center of image. (Drawer E 14, Folder 1)
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    Rolled and torn edges. Stains from adhesive tape. Note on verso "Old map of P.H. showing houses, including JDR, Show boys, take home".
  - "William W. Carson Farm, Town of Mount Pleasant, Westchester County, NY," maps whose property belonging to JDR, property of Consolidated Water Company of Suburban New York and William Rockefeller, 1913; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 10, Folder 1)
    PH 12
    note on reverse "1913 W.W. Carson property adjoining Wm. Rockefeller Land
  - Map of Fire Hydrants, Area of Pocantico Hills Estate, 1935; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1). Oversized. (Drawer F 10, Folder 1)
    PH 30
    noted on reverse "J.G. White Engineering Co maps showing additions to water mains and showing fire hydrants at P.H. in 1933"
  - "Topography of a Portion of Property 166-1/2 Acre Tract, Westchester County, NY." Indicates lands JDR Sr. was willing to lease for golf course., 1928 May; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 10, Folder 1)
    PH 32, copy 1
    noted "May 1928 Mandel & Rockwood Club property with stakes indicating land Mr. R. is willing to lease for golf course"
  - "Relocation of Putnam Branch Between Eastview & Briarcliff Manor & Connection with Harlem Division at Hawthorne." (NYCRR Buffalo & East - Putnam Division - Engineering Department), 1925; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 10, Folder 1)
    PH-65, PH 38A
    noted on reverse "Feb 1925. Blueprint from NY Central sent to files June 1930 by Mr. Heydt. Marked in red. Properties approved for acquisition for Saw Mill River Parkway by Westchester County Parks Comm."
  - Topographical Map of Tarrytown and Sleepy Hollow Manor, 1924 December; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 10, Folder 1)
    PH 24
    noted on reverse "Tarrytown-Sleepy Hollow manor topo map used by Mr. Rockefeller. Sent by JA Smith".
  - 4 Topographical drawings of Christian Brothers' property, 1929-1930; MAP (Quantity 4) (Drawer F 10, Folder 1)
    PH 19A, 71
    noted on reverse "Christian Brothers Property 1929. Leavitt topo map", "Kidde Map-Christian Brothers Property"
  - 3 copies of "Map of Tarrytown and Environs, Westchester Co., NY." with marginalia, 1936 January; MAP (Quantity 3). Oversized. (Drawer F 10, Folder 1)
    PH-29
  - Map of Mt. Pleasant, North Tarrytown, Greenburg, Tarrytown, and Elmsburg, w/ handwritten notes & coloring, MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 10, Folder 1)
  - Topographical Survey of Rockefeller Family Properties Surrounding Tarrytown., MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 10, Folder 1)
    PH-101
  - "Survey at Pocantico Hills Gate, Shop, Gardens, and Old Boarding House." Map showing property of Bodelson. (Walter Kidde Constructors Inc.), 1931 December 18; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 10, Folder 1)
    PH-95
  - series of elevations for "Proposed Indoor Tennis Court at Pocantico Hills New York" (Duncan Candler- Architect), 1937; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 5) (Drawer F 10, Folder 1)
  - 2 copies of map of property of Town of Mount Pleasant & Town of Greenburgh, NY, w/ coloring and notes (Chas H. Sells), 1972 December; MAP (Quantity 2) (Drawer F 10, Folder 1)
  - "Survey of Pocantico Hills Church and adjoining property...", 1929 June; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer F 10, Folder 1)
    PH 67
    note on reverse reads "Survey of Pocantico Hill Church and adjoining property (showing new property line and relation of new addition to same"
  - Map of the Property of John D. Rockefeller situated in Pocantico Hills, Westchester NY. On mylar., MAP (Quantity 1). Ovesized. (Drawer B 5, Folder 1)
    Restricted from scholarly access. Requires permission from Historic Hudson Valley.
  - "Map of JDR Property: Pocantico Hills", Blueprint negative. (Engineering Department of NY), 1928 June 27; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1). Oversized. (Drawer B 5, Folder 1)
    PH 65
  - Map of plan for transmission lines leading to Pocantico Hills", 1942 December; MAP (Quantity 1). Oversized. (Drawer B 5, Folder 1)
    PH 91B
  - Map of lands to be acquired for Saw Mill River Parkway, land donation maps of John D. Rockefeller Jr. Westchester County Park Commission., 1930 July 28; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 5) (Drawer B 5, Folder 1)
    PH no.90, maps no-3655-3659
  - Photocopy of "Map of the Property of John D. Rockefeller situated in Pocantico Hills, Westchester, NY.", MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 5, Folder 1)
  - "Map of proposed purchase of John D. Rockefeller parcel of land" (Westchester Lighting Company: Mount Pleasant, NY), 1942 April 30; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 5, Folder 1)
    PH no.91
  - Map of purchase of John D. Rockefeller parcel of land, revised map showing property to be deeded to Westchester Lighting Company for transmission lines: Mount Pleasant, NY, 1942 July; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 5, Folder 1)
    PH no.91a
  - Organizational chart of Pocantico Hills Estate employees, 1933 December 4; GRAPH (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 5, Folder 1)
    PH no. 40
  - "Relocation of Putnam Branch & Briarcliff Manor." Photographic Negative., 1928 June 27; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 5, Folder 2)
  - "Map of Tarrytown and Vicinity." (Ward Carpenter & Son), 1880; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 5, Folder 2)
  - “Diagram Map of Property Belonging to John D. Rockefeller Jr. Situated at Pocantico Hills, Westchester County NY,". Key map to Earl B. Lovell (Lawyers Title and Guaranty Company) survey of Pocantico Hills estate, showing exact boundaries. Index to section maps 1-7, 1933 April 24; revised: 1933 May; 2 Sheets 2 copies: 1 original color map; 1 photocopy,; MAP (Quantity 2) (Drawer B 5, Folder 1)
    PH 57A
  - Map of Property Belonging to John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Situated at Pocantico Hills, Westchester County, New York, Section Map Number 1, 1931 November; amended 1933 March; 1 Sheets Scale: 1 inch = 100 feet 86.5” x 30” (Case Rolled Maps Unit 1, Sheet Slot B1)
    Earl B. Lovell (Lawyers Title and Guaranty Company) survey of Rockefeller Estate in Pocantico Hills, NY. Section 1 map covers eastern boundary of Pocantico Hills estate along Buttermilk Hill, and includes estate boundary monuments 1 – 180.
    Related Materials
    Office of the Messrs. Rockefeller records, Homes, Series I (FA318), Property: Pocantico Hills, NY, Pocantico Hills - Property - Survey by Lawyers - Title and Guaranty, 1930-1949, Box 53, Folders 540 - 541
    Conditions Governing Access
  - Map of Property Belonging to John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Situated at Pocantico Hills, Westchester County, New York, Section Map Number 2, 1931 November; amended 1933 March; 1 Sheets Scale: 1 inch = 100 feet 44” x 30.5” (Case Rolled Maps Unit 1, Sheet Slot B2)
    Earl B. Lovell (Lawyers Title and Guaranty Company) survey of Rockefeller Estate in Pocantico Hills, NY. Section 2 map covers central portion of Pocantico Hills estate, between Sleepy Hollow Road and Bedford Road, and includes estate boundary monuments 181 – 377.
  - Map of Property Belonging to John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Situated at Pocantico Hills, Westchester County, New York, Section Map Number 3, 1931 November; amended 1933 March; 1 Sheets Scale: 1 inch = 100 feet 52.5” x 30” (Case Rolled Maps Unit 1, Sheet Slot B3)
    Separated Materials
    Earl B. Lovell (Lawyers Title and Guaranty Company) survey of Rockefeller Estate in Pocantico Hills, NY. Section 3 map covers north-western portion of Pocantico Hills estate, south of Sleepy Hollow Road, and includes estate boundary monuments 378 – 513.
  - Map of Property Belonging to John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Situated at Pocantico Hills, Westchester County, New York, Section Map Number 4, 1931 November; amended 1933 March; 1 Sheets Scale: 1 inch = 100 feet 44.5” x 23” (Case Rolled Maps Unit 1, Sheet Slot B4)
    Earl B. Lovell (Lawyers Title and Guaranty Company) survey of Rockefeller Estate in Pocantico Hills, NY. Section 4 map covers western portion of Pocantico Hills estate in the Pocantico River valley, and includes estate boundary monuments 514 – 573.
  - Map of Property Belonging to John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Situated at Pocantico Hills, Westchester County, New York, Section Map Number 5, 1931 November; amended 1933 March; 1 Sheets Scale: 1 inch = 100 feet 63” x 25” (Case Rolled Maps Unit 1, Sheet Slot B5)
    Earl B. Lovell (Lawyers Title and Guaranty Company) survey of Rockefeller Estate in Pocantico Hills, NY. Section 5 map covers south-western portion of Pocantico Hills estate along Weber Avenue, and includes estate boundary monuments 574 – 638.
  - Map of Property Belonging to John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Situated at Pocantico Hills, Westchester County, New York, Section Map Number 6, 1931 November; amended 1933 March; 1 Sheets Scale: 1 inch = 100 feet 39” x 30” (Case Rolled Maps Unit 1, Sheet Slot B6)
    Earl B. Lovell (Lawyers Title and Guaranty Company) survey of Rockefeller Estate in Pocantico Hills, NY. Section 6 map covers central portion of Pocantico Hills estate around Kykuit, and includes estate boundary monuments 639 – 791.
  - Map of Property Belonging to John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Situated at Pocantico Hills, Westchester County, New York, Section Map Number 7, 1931 November; amended 1933 March; 1 Sheets Scale: 1 inch = 100 feet 37” x 30” (Case Rolled Maps Unit 1, Sheet Slot B7)
    Earl B. Lovell (Lawyers Title and Guaranty Company) survey of Rockefeller Estate in Pocantico Hills, NY. Section 7 map covers southern portion of Pocantico Hills estate around the Tarrytown reservoirs, and includes estate boundary monuments 792 – 931.
- Hillcrest, 7
  - Survey of Property prepared for The Hills Realty Co., with duplicates, 1960 August 3; MAP (Quantity 3) (Drawer B 8, Folder 1)
    J-60-373
  - Series of photocopied blueprints for Hillcrest (grounds, house, and individual rooms)., BLUEPRINT (Drawer B 8, Folder 2)
  - Folder containing archival and original copies of original gate house to Hillcrest., 1963 March; BLUEPRINT (Drawer B 8, Folder 2)
  - Series of original positive blueprints to Service Gate House at Hillcrest., BLUEPRINT (Drawer B 8, Folder 2)
  - landscaping map to Hillcrest grounds., 1964 April 22; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 8, Folder 2)
  - photocopy of landscaping map above., MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer B 8, Folder 2)
  - Series (31) of brown architectural maps of the grounds and house of the Rockefeller Archive Center., 1974 June 25; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 31). Oversized. (Drawer B 8, Folder 3)
  - Series (33) of blue and white architectural maps (copies & originals) of the RAC., 1977 December 12; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 33) (Drawer B 8, Folder 4)
  - grounds layout and outdoor furnishing options for Hillcrest archives., 1974 April 11 and 1975 May 5; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 2) (Drawer D 6, Folder 1)
  - Westchester County Vol.4 Town of Mt. Pleasant (G.M. Hopkins Co, Philadelphia PA), 1930; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 7, Folder 1)
    Former Classification: III 2 M
  - "Scheme C" elevation drawings of house (Mott B. Schmidt), 1961 November-December; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 4) (Drawer E 7, Folder 1)
  - "Office of JDR JR; Somerville Drawings for Installation at RAC, Pocantico Hills, NY" (Mott B. Schmidt), 1975 May 15. Revised: 1975 June 4; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 3) (Drawer E 7, Folder 1)
  - elevations and plan of "House for Mrs. JDR JR, Pocantico Hills, NY" (Mott B. Schmidt), 1962 April 16. Revised: 1962 June 27 and July 12; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 8) (Drawer E 7, Folder 1)
  - elevations and plans of "Mrs. JDR JR, Pocantico Hills, NY" (Mott B. Schmidt), 1963 December 4; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 4) (Drawer E 7, Folder 1)
  - elevations and plans of "Mrs. JDR JR, Pocantico Hills, NY" (Mott B. Schmidt), 1962 April 16. Revised: 1962-1964; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 10) (Drawer E 7, Folder 1)
  - booklet of preliminary elevations "Hillcrest Archives" (Goldstone, Dearborn & Heinz/David Hiat), 1972 June 28; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 16) (Drawer E 7, Folder 1)
  - sheets A1-A12, P2, S1-S7 of elevations for Hillcrest Archives (RAC) (Goldstone & Heinz), 1974 April 11; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 21) (Drawer E 12, Folder 1)
  - 2 floorplans, Levels B and C, of Hillcrest Archives (RAC) (Goldstone & Hinz), 1973 October 16; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 2) (Drawer E 12, Folder 1)
  - Tree Survey of Rockefeller University Archive Center (Alpine Environmental Services), MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 12, Folder 1)
  - Plans for the Installation of Meters, Meter Pits & Water Main for Greenrock Corporation, Pocantico Hills NY (Chas H. Sells), 1973 February; MAP (Quantity 3) (Drawer E 12, Folder 1)
  - survey of property for JDR JR in Pocantico Hills NY (Walter Kidde, Constructors Inc., NYC), 1942 May 4; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 12, Folder 1)
- Rockwood Hall, 8
  - Topographical Map of Rockwood. Digital reprint, 1887; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 8, Folder 1)
  - Rockwood Hall Property map. Aerial photo with map overlay. (H. Stanley Johnson, Mt. Kisco, NY), 1982 November 1; MAP (Quantity 8) (Drawer E 8, Folder 1)
  - Site Plan Alternative, Rockwood Hall Park Entrance. Topographical. (Sasaki Associates, Inc. (Massachusetts)), 1984 July 2; MAP (Quantity 4) (Drawer E 8, Folder 1)
  - Road Map of the estate of Mr. John D. Rockefeller Jr. at Pocantico Hills (Walter Kidde, Constructors Inc., NYC), 1932 July 2. Revised: 1937 May 1; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 8, Folder 1)
    Separated from collection.
  - Study for a State Park at Rockwood Hall (Vollmer Associates), undated; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 8, Folder 1)
  - Bottom soundings of Rockwood Hall (Keuffel & Esser Co.), MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 15, Folder 1)
  - "Proposed Golf Course on Property Belonging to William Rockefeller Estate, Town of Mt. Pleasant, NY" (Ward Carpenter & Co.), 1923 December 14; MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 1, Folder 1)
    Accession 2010:003.
  - Rockwood Hall, Rockefeller State Park Preserve (Imbiano-Quigley Landscape Architects, P.C.), MAP (Quantity 1) (Drawer Q 1, Folder 1)
    Immediate Source of Acquisition note
- Laurance S. Rockefeller, 9
  - Office of the Messrs. Rockefeller files, 9.1
    - "arrangement study" for commuter boat (Sparkman & Stevens Inc.), 1945 October 30 and November 9; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 11, Folder 1)
    - 3 drawings for commuter boat (Sparkman & Stevens Inc.), 1946 April; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 3) (Drawer E 11, Folder 1)
    - Design for commuter boat (Sparkman & Stevens Inc.), 1948 December 23; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 11, Folder 1)
    - "Proposed Memorial for JDR JR." (Harrison & Abramowitz, architects), 1961 February 14. Received: 1961 February 16; WHITEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 11, Folder 2)
    - "Details of Glass Bottom Reflectors on 2 display cases, at LSR apartment 115 E. 67th St NY NY" (Mott B. Schmidt), 1941 May 14; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 11, Folder 2)
    - "Design #361" drawing for passenger boat; note on reverse to "Miss Wells" from 5/16/40 (Sparkman & Stevens Inc.), 1940 May 6; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 11, Folder 2)
    - "Concrete Barge Type B: Lines," "Proposal for the Construction of Concrete Barges Shipshape without Crew Design for United States Maritime Commission" (Concrete Ship Building Co. Inc.), 1941 September 29; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 11, Folder 2)
    - arrangement study "W.L. Commuter Boat" (Sparkman & Stevens Inc.), 1945 October 30; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 11, Folder 2)
    - "Design #339 Proposed L.W.L. Commuter" boat design (Sparkman & Stevens Inc.), 1940 January 29; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 11, Folder 2)
    - 2 sketches "Alteration to Residence for LSR" possible source: (Mott B. Schmidt), 1951 March 2 ?; ARCHITECTURAL DRAWING (Quantity 2) (Drawer E 11, Folder 2)
    - topographic survey prepared for LSR, Pocantico Hills Westchester NY; with writing on it (Chas H. Sells), 1937-1938; BLUEPRINT (Quantity 1) (Drawer E 11, Folder 2)